// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following developed Java?",
    answer: "James Gosling",
    options: [
      "James Gosling",
      "Bjarne Stroustroup",
      "Larry Wall",
      "Rasmus Lardorf"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following developed C language?",
    answer: "Dennis Ritchie",
    options: [
      "Brendan Eich",
      "Bjarne Stroustroup",
      "Dennis Ritchie",
      "Rasmus Lardorf"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following developed Python language? ",
    answer: "Guido van Rossum",
    options: [
      "James Gosling",
      "Brendan Eich",
      "Larry Wall",
      "Guido van Rossum"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following developed C++ language?",
    answer: "Bjarne Stroustroup",
    options: [
      "James Gosling",
      "Bjarne Stroustroup",
      "Larry Wall",
      "Rasmus Lardorf"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following developed Ruby language?",
    answer: "Yukihiro Matsumoto",
    options: [
      "Guido van Rossum",
      "Brendan Eich",
      "Yukihiro Matsumoto",
      "Guido van Rossum"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following developed PHP language?",
    answer: "Rasmus Lardorf",
    options: [
      "Yukihiro Matsumoto",
      "Bjarne Stroustroup",
      "Guido van Rossum",
      "Rasmus Lardorf"
    ]
  },

  {  numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following developed Lisp language?",
    answer: "John McCarthy",
    options: [
      "James Gosling",
      "John McCarthy",
      "Yukihiro Matsumoto",
      "Guido van Rossum"
    ]
  },

  {  
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following developed Perl language?",
    answer: "Larry Wall",
    options: [
      "Yukihiro Matsumoto",
      "John McCarthy",
      "Larry Wall",
      "Rasmus Lardorf"
    ]
  },

  {  
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following developed Pascal language?",
    answer: "Niklaus Wirth",
    options: [
      "James Gosling",
      "John McCarthy",
      "Niklaus Wirth",
      "Guido van Rossum"
    ]
  },

  {  
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following developed JavaScript language?",
    answer: "Applet Class.",
    options: [
      "James Gosling",
      "Bjarne Stroustroup",
      "Brendan Eich",
      "Guido van Rossum"
    ]
  },
];
